extremefreecoupons.com 2014-02-12

# Privacy Policy - Extreme Free Coupons - www.extremefreecoupons.com - Save up to 90% Today!

**Effective July 06, 2011**  
Thank you for visiting ExtremeFreeCoupons.com (the "Site"). The Site is an Internet property of Send Interactive Media Inc. and its affiliated companies ("Send Interactive", "we" or "us"). This Privacy Policy outlines the privacy practices associated with the Site and by accessing and using the Site, you hereby agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety.

The Site does not collect any personally identifiable information, however, it may contain links to other third party sites that we believe may be of interest to you. 

Please be advised that Send Interactive does not itself provide the featured products or services, or any other related products and services. The Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy of any featured products and/or services provided by any third party providers will be determined by those third party providers and it is your responsibility to review and accept those agreements prior to your access and use of such websites. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit the Site. This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation, the type of browser that you use (e.g., Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome), your IP address, the type of operating system that you use (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider. We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Site, to analyze Site usage, and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also reserve the right to use aggregate or group data about our visitors for any and all lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage and/or characteristics of our visitors as a group.

**Cookies**  
When an end-user visits the Site, we send a cookie and/or gif file ("Cookie") to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to the applicable end-user's Internet browser. A Cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing non-personally identifiable information about you. Cookies have many benefits to enhance your experience at the Site. To disable and reject certain Cookies, follow the instructions associated with your Internet browser. Even in the case where a user rejects a Cookie, he or she may still use this Site. Send Interactive reserves the right to retain Cookie data indefinitely.

**Third Party Links**  
The Website may contain links to other third-party owned and/or operated websites and Send Interactive may transfer you directly to the websites of such third party providers. Send Interactive is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In some cases, you may be required to provide certain information to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third-party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and Send Interactive has no responsibility or liability relating to them. We do not endorse, nor are we responsible for the accuracy of, the privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of such website. These third party entities are independent third parties and are not affiliated with us.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice to you. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. Please check the Site periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site and/or acceptance of our e-mail communications following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions regarding this statement, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please CONTACT US
